<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xwikidoc>
<web>BatchImport</web>
<name>Translations</name>
<language></language>
<defaultLanguage>en</defaultLanguage>
<translation>0</translation>
<parent></parent>
<creator>XWiki.Admin</creator>
<author>XWiki.Admin</author>
<customClass></customClass>
<contentAuthor>XWiki.Admin</contentAuthor>
<creationDate>1341566618000</creationDate>
<date>1341576679000</date>
<contentUpdateDate>1341576679000</contentUpdateDate>
<version>1.1</version>
<title></title>
<template></template>
<defaultTemplate></defaultTemplate>
<validationScript></validationScript>
<comment></comment>
<minorEdit>false</minorEdit>
<syntaxId>xwiki/2.1</syntaxId>
<hidden>false</hidden>
<content>batchimport.import.overwrite.title=Data deduplication and overwrite
batchimport.import.overwrite.deduplication.explanation=If by any chance, the column chose for document name does not contain unique names, what should happen to the **duplicate rows**?
batchimport.import.overwrite.deduplication.option.skip=Ignore
batchimport.import.overwrite.deduplication.option.update=Update: use the data as part of the other rows with the same document name (if the same column is set on multiple rows, the last one will win).
batchimport.import.overwrite.deduplication.option.generate_new=Generate a new document name, by adding a number at the end of the document name
batchimport.import.overwrite.explanation=If then, for the document name built as indicated above, a document already exists in the wiki with that name, what should we to the **existing document in the wiki**?
batchimport.import.overwrite.option.skip=Leave unchanged (ignore data from the file)
batchimport.import.overwrite.option.update=Update with the data coming from the file (the fields mapped on the columns of the file will be updated, the rest will remain unchanged)
batchimport.import.overwrite.option.replace=Replace with the data coming from the file (the existing document will be deleted and a new one will be created instead, containing only the data in the file)
batchimport.import.overwrite.option.generate_new=Generate a new document name, by adding a number at the end of the document name built as indicated above. Note that 2 subsequent imports with this option checked will not yield the same results since the document names used depend on the documents existing on the wiki.

</content></xwikidoc>